hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast
my name is Jeremiah Krakowski and if we
haven't met yet I help coaches trainers
mentors and entrepreneurs that want to
help make an impact in people's lives
with their knowledge and information
scale their businesses to 20 and even 40
000 per month
many of our clients have even gone on to
make tens of millions of dollars using
the information that we teach and so
today I want to help you with one of the
most powerful
Frameworks for reaching your goals that
exists
and something that has really
transformed my life
I've been wanting to pass on to my
clients here's the thing
we all know where we
want to be in life
but
we often
get caught up in
complaining
and disappointment that we're not there
yet
and this way of thinking
while we may believe
is going to help us reach our goals long
term because we're focusing on what we
need to be doing and what we're not
doing yet and
we're
so focused on
okay this is the task but this is why I
can't do it and we're looking at our
problem and solution
here's the problem with that this is why
that doesn't work
this is why most
of the ways that we've been trained to
reach our goals especially as business
owners don't work first off
99 of people
the way that they're taught goals
works for Corporate America
works for if you're in a college setting
works for if you are an employee
working for somebody else and so realize
that
the one percent or the two percent of
people that are actually
self-employed and making a quarter of a
million to a half a million dollars a
year right because that's what we're
we're thinking about you're not going to
reach that income level
with the same level of thinking and
behavior that keeps you below that level
and truthfully
most people don't earn that much
people think it's impossible to earn
that much
and so there's a number of Frameworks
that a I developed that have helped us
last month we made 160 000 in our
business
and our lowest month
I would say the lowest amount of income
that I've made in the last
five to seven years I don't like the
exact timeline but is it hasn't dropped
below 20 000 a month so
we haven't made less than a quarter of a
million dollars in our family in our
lifestyle
and these Frameworks have helped okay so
hear from me if you're somebody that
wants to make multiple six figures or
even seven figures this will break you
out of the box of that the first one is
this
imagine the life you want
have a vision for it
and here's the Temptation with that we
immediately start coming up with why we
can't have that life what needs to
change
that's actually not going to help you
focusing so much on what needs to change
focusing so much on what's not working
focusing so much on what you
wish was different
is not going to produce
the kind of life or results that you
want now it's a natural human tendency
we don't need any help to do that
our brains
are actually pre-wired to do that for
survival okay so you have to break out
of your pre-wired survival mechanisms
to be able to step into a thriving
framework okay
now here's the next one is
and most people
don't do this
until they reach a certain level of
success
and I would
encourage you
that this is a success framework that
will actually get you success rather
than something to wait until you have
success to do and what that is is that
is
congratulating yourself
for every little thing that you do that
you accomplish encouraging yourself oh I
woke up
two hours earlier this morning not man
I'm just doing what I should
give yourself a high five and say you
know what I'm doing great today I'm
doing my best
I'm giving it my best
when we do this we allow ourselves to
rewire our brain towards abundance
towards happiness towards looking at the
best case scenario and out of survival
as well
we can really get caught up in this I'm
not good enough mentality this I'm not
doing good enough and so I need to be
doing more and and the truth is we don't
need any help to do that we can look at
what are we doing every single day
what's not working okay
what do we need to do what needs to
change
and we we have those answers right away
but here's here's the truth
most people I meet have the answers of
what they need to do already
like
I need to go through a course
I need to listen to more podcasts I need
to spend more time
writing my sales copy creating my
landing page like they know what they
need to do okay I need to come up with
my niche
I need to ask for help maybe I need to
join a coaching program maybe I need to
get a mentor okay
so we
naturally know what we need to do
we naturally
like
already have that figured out but we
what we do is we end up ruminating on
what's not working
and thinking about and overthinking
about what needs to happen
that's a survival mechanism and that
comes from
it's a natural human thing
trying to protect ourselves
trying to make sure that things don't go
bad
trying to make sure
that the last shoe doesn't drop
and for those of you that if you've
experienced that touch your whole life
like I did Growing Up
um it's very
difficult to actually rewire and retrain
that
but
it's something that it's going to be the
most difficult thing that you'll ever do
in your life I think
is to rewire and retrain that
but with intention the more you do it it
becomes a habit and it becomes a
habit framework
that you can start doing more of
every single day in your life
in your business
to take a look at okay
instead of me focusing on what's not
working instead of me focusing on what I
wish was different
instead of me focusing on what needs to
change
or what I want right because we think
about okay I have a vision for the
future
I have this vision for how I want my
life to be
and so
Jeremiah says have a vision and so then
all we focus on is what we need to
change what we want to change what we're
not happy with what we're disappointed
about
that's not what I'm talking about at all
I'm talking about from a place of
declaration
and belief
and abundance
that
I'm seeing my best life before it
happens
and I'm seeing it without
attachment
expectation and that's one of the
biggest
key factors is
getting rid of attachment
and expectation
to outcomes
and needing
things to go the way that we envision
the truth is that as we get started as
we move towards our goals as we start to
create the life that we want things
aren't going to go
always how we envisioned that we might
have a plan
for how we would like things to go
we might have a plan for how we would
Envision would be best for us but then
when reality kind of smacks you in the
face
you're like man nothing's going my way
nothing's going how I want it to and
this creates
the perpetual
never-ending cycle
of disappointment and regret and feeling
like
I can't ever get ahead no matter what I
do nothing works out for me nothing goes
my way people like us that don't succeed
and we replay these statements over and
over again you have this ups and downs
of motivation
demotivation motivation demotivation
motivation demotivation and you're not
actually making any progress or you're
making very slow progress right
and so really what I'm what I'm helping
you with is I want you to be able to
compress time
I want you to be able to shrink
timelines
in your normal everyday life you might
have a timeline that okay it's going to
take me five to ten years to accomplish
this
but I want to accomplish it in a year or
two or six months
and and
really truly we all want that
but if we were honest with ourselves at
the end of the day that's not reality
that's not what we're experiencing
this is the only one
framework that I know that can actually
compress timelines
that actually does shrink that down is
by congratulating yourself
by encouraging yourself even when you
mess up even when you make a mistake
even when you fail even when things
don't go your way
congratulate yourself and I'm giving it
my best shot
being thankful for
however anything went
seeing things more as an experiment
rather than
like requiring that outcome to go how it
is well I require it to go this way you
we have to really break up with even
that type of language
that well I'm not going to be happy
until
I reached this place
I used to find myself saying that all
the time
and realizing that your happiness comes
from inside it doesn't come from
the results you produce it doesn't come
from
what you're creating it doesn't come
how you perform
now that might not be how you've lived
your life up to this moment in time
maybe you've lived your life up to this
moment in time that your happiness is
only based off of
final outcomes
that's only based off of
the end goal
and that way of living I've lived it for
years
will work
directly against
you actually reaching your goals and you
might say well Jeremiah I've reached a
lot of goals doing that
I would I would beg to argue you've
reached your goals in spite of that
not because of
and that it was more your persistence
and tenacity and not giving up
that actually allows you to reach those
goals rather than that behavior
produce the result
because every single millionaire that
I've talked to in my own life
I have found that this
type of
detaching from the outcome
letting go
of how we need things to be letting go
of expectations letting go
of well if it doesn't go my way then I'm
going to be unhappy letting go
of
requiring stuff
to go our way
for our joy and happiness and instead
saying you know what
I'm gonna give it my best shot
it's all an experiment
I'm just gonna see what happens and I'm
gonna be I'm gonna be good
no matter what happens I'm gonna be good
no matter how something goes
that my
safety security
happiness certainty
is not tied to
producing the goal it's not tied to my
performance my worth
is not tied to
how I perform
that my worth
does not come from if I can produce this
result or not
and that we completely detach and let go
of our identity
our happiness and our joy being related
to
performance metrics
okay
now in business obviously we look we
look at performance metrics to help us
make decisions if our actions or choices
are working
but we have to remove the emotion from
it we have to remove the feeling of good
enough
from it I'll tell you this every single
person watching this right now you're
you're a hundred and ten percent
already good enough
and already
even skilled enough
to make a six-figure coaching business
and you might not believe it but I'm
telling you in my experience
it doesn't take any more skill
or knowledge or even experience to make
six figures
so borrow my belief borrow my faith
borrow the fact that I know that from
working with
thousands of coaches mentors trainers
people over the years
and then looking at the ones who are
successful
versus the ones who really struggle the
ones who really
don't see the result that they want the
ones who really they've been struggling
for years
I take a look at
what are they doing
and then what are the people that are
successful doing that's different
and then what am I doing that has made
success
and so what I'm telling you right now
isn't just from some ideas that I've
read in a book
or heard on a podcast
this is solid
experience
that has created
the life that I live the life that I
could have only dreamed of
years ago
you know yes I come from a background
where I've been in the industry for a
long time but I always thought that I
was going to have to work for somebody
else and help somebody else's vision and
truly I didn't
think that I had what it takes for years
to make the kind of money that I'm
making
and I was happy with just a
you know twenty thirty thousand dollars
a month
now we've surpassed that to even seven
figures
and what got me to twenty thirty
thousand dollars a month is the same
mentality framework that's got me to
seven figures but it's like
okay
why is it that most people don't do this
I've been teaching this message
for years
I've taught it
for a long time but most people
don't grab onto it they're they're too
critical of themselves
they're too self-punishing
they're too attached to how they need
things to go
they
are too attached to how they require
things to be or they don't feel good
enough
and when we just let all that stuff go
and you just go out there and build your
business as one big fun experiment where
you literally don't care how it goes
you might be saying Jeremiah that sounds
irresponsible
yeah
I guess
you got to do the Reckless irresponsible
thing sometimes sometimes
if we are
that concerned
about
needing to operate in such a rigid
framework
of perfection and responsibility and
doing all the right things I was raised
that way I was raised to never do
anything unless it's perfect
unless you can guarantee a result and
that there's no risk and that if you do
that you are a bad harmful person that
doesn't take care of their family and
you are irresponsible and in fact that
that even God rejects you for doing that
that's how I was raised
okay
and so I know that framework of thinking
I know that framework of thinking we
have to like
rewire our brains
if we want to increase our income as
business owners we have to start
thinking
living
making different choices making
different decisions and looking at the
world differently
than what got us here
and now I want to I want to encourage
you
that the fact that you're even listening
to this right now give yourself a high
five you're doing what most people won't
do most people will find a podcast
episode like this and shut it off in the
first five minutes because it made them
feel very uncomfortable
and so
the fact that you're even able to listen
to this right now
shows me that you're open to stepping
into the next level of your life
that you're stepping into the next level
of creating the life that you want
because you're you're able to
take a look internally at maybe what
I've been doing isn't working
and you're not letting Pride or ego
step in to argue for your limitations
you're not fighting for what hasn't been
working in your life
you're not fighting for your upbringing
I meet people every single week they
tell me Well Jeremiah
my culture and how I was raised taught
me to not be that way and so I can't
change and I'm like
no no you're you're you're choosing not
to change that's definitely a choice but
we got some deeper issues there you
might need to work through some trauma
you might need to work through realizing
that how you've always been taught to do
something you're not required or
obligated to always do that in the
future
and I want you to start to think about
as I've talked about this hey two things
okay here's an exercise of how to apply
this in your life
one
if you started doing this
how would your life change
what changes would you see happen
for you
what would be different
in your life
some of you see
immediately will get a vision of all
your dreams coming true others of you
will get a vision of
a lot of pain suffering and people
hating you and your whole life being
destroyed
if that's the case and you're like my
whole life would be destroyed
I want you to journal out
and write down all those things because
what that's pointing to is you have
beliefs that are based off of
experiences and not wanting to
invalidate those experiences at all
because your experiences have taught you
these things
you have beliefs
that are telling you that it's
impossible for you to do what I've
talked about
that you can't that people like you
can't or bad things will happen to you
and and here's what I'll say I'll get it
I get it
if I was still with the same friends
hanging out with the same family members
talking to the same people and doing the
same things in the same job
that I had started this journey with
absolutely I couldn't operate in that
framework
and so we literally have to
get new friends
stop asking for advice from the same old
same old people
find new people to listen to
if you listen to my podcast it's going
to change your life if you plug into my
social media every single day I make
posts to help course creators and
coaches change their life in their
business
we got a coaching program with all of
the skills that you need to learn
on how to Market and sell and build your
funnels and write your sales copy and
grow your email list
these are the expert strategies
that have scaled our business that are
skilled our clients businesses to tens
of millions of dollars that have scaled
our clients businesses maybe they don't
want to make tens of millions but scaled
them to multiple six figures
and so if you hang out with me
it's going to change your thinking and
you're going to get into my community as
well and start thinking the way that our
community members do we got people that
you can hang out with new friends that
you can make
in our community
that will help change your life
but you got to make the choice and the
desire that I want my life changed if
you have no desire
nothing's gonna happen
if you're just going to keep going the
Motions the same old same old nothing's
gonna happen
and so you you gotta
you gotta make some choices some
decisions you don't need to make them
today but I would recommend maybe you
make them sometime in the next month
right
this is something my therapist taught me
she's like
you know sometimes it's like okay if I
didn't make the choice today then it's
I'm a failure no give yourself a month
or two to make these choices give
yourself a transition period to work out
some of those feelings inside of you of
of
why you think this stuff won't work out
Journal it out
talk with some of your friends about
this if if you share some of the ideas
that you got on this podcast and some of
you are going to listen to this episode
multiple times over
during the next month or so
because it's going to change the way you
think and then you're gonna get
something new out of it each time
the Frameworks I've just mentioned to
you
will absolutely change your life
and your business and your income you're
detached from outcomes
you stop
worrying about what other people think
about you so you stop caring about how
people perceive you not that you don't
care about other people
I care a lot about people I love people
I don't do what I do because I hate
people
but I also don't spend time in business
with people that aren't paying me money
or that don't have a producing result
I've had people call me arrogant and
tell me that there's more things to life
than money Jeremiah you got to get over
yourself and I'm just like
I run a business and so I'm not going to
be spending time with people that aren't
paying me money in business
for business stuff because I got
employees to pay family defeat like you
know it's just ridiculous
but that's the thing we get
we got all these voices in our life that
try to contradict
the truth and try to contradict
what's actually going to get you to
where you want to go
and so I want you to notice as you
listen through this podcast what does it
bring up in you was it Inspire what does
it make you feel
Journal that out
write it down
and then come back to it and see okay
what am I believing behind this what
beliefs do I have about what's possible
for me
my family
and my business that are preventing me
from being able to start living
the way that Jeremiah talks in this
episode
see I could teach you all the strategies
and I do I have them go scroll through
all the podcast episodes there's tons of
strategy
but if you don't get this
if you don't get this mental framework
those strategies will
fall flat
detach from the outcome let go of
needing things to go a certain way
just experiment just have fun
be okay with things failing
be okay with them not working out
and keep moving forward
and and this one's above all keep
congratulating yourself just for your
progress
keep giving yourself a high five stop
waiting until the Finish Line to do so
be like a runner you got all those
people that give them the high five and
a marathon each step they take because
each step is a breakthrough of of of
breaking past those limitations each
step forward you want to start
congratulating yourself not at each
Milestone I used to do this this is one
of the biggest things that even this
year
I've started to change in my life
is congratulating myself
for each Milestone rather than at each
Finish Line
and it'll revolutionize your life this
one habit of giving yourself a high five
multiple times a day
for giving it your best even when you
fail even when you mess up even when you
yell at your spouse or yell at your kids
or or you make a a decision that didn't
turn out well
you congratulate yourself and you keep
moving forward
let's change everything for you my
friends
one of the last things is we got to take
personal responsibility in our lives
and this is this is one of the hardest
things that people
need to learn is
I I would say I learned this one early
on
and it helped a lot is nobody in life is
to blame for why you are where you are
but you
and that might sound hard because I know
we've been through a lot
and you might have even been a victim of
abuse
and had a terrible childhood and all
that I've been through that as well
but I want to say this
the choices we make are on us
the choices I make to let what happened
to me Define me that's on me not what
somebody else did to me
and the other thing is this is
motivation is fleeting you might feel
motivated after hearing this
and keep listening to podcasts and
training because it'll amp you up it'll
get you motivated it'll get you fired up
to do the great things
but like
motivation's fleeting
and that's why we need to develop
self-discipline that even when we don't
feel like doing it
we still get up and do it
I didn't feel like recording this
podcast episode this morning truthfully
but I gave myself a high five for going
out there and doing it you know what I
know that it came out great because I
did that because discipline showed up
where my motivation was lacking
and I know that by doing that
that changes the game
most people lack the ability to do what
they don't feel like doing it's not that
you're stuffing your feelings you
actually want to pay attention to what
are your feelings telling you for me I
identified them
and I work through them
and but I also know I gotta
I gotta deliver a podcast people I got
people that that want me to deliver
and I want to if I want to impact people
the way that I know that I'm called and
was born to do I gotta press record and
I got to talk to y'all so
discipline developing self-discipline
that's where Freedom comes from
discipline is freedom
and taking personal responsibility
extreme ownership ownership over
everything in your life that I am
responsible for how things go
you might say yeah but like God is in
control isn't he this doesn't violate
the laws of
of Faith this doesn't go against our
beliefs about
God and and and his Almighty power at
all what I'm talking about is if if
you're not currently experiencing in
your life right now something
you got to take a look at
what needs to change who I need who I
need to talk to different
where do I need to go what behaviors
need to be different
what
is not working currently
and stop blaming other people stop
blaming even God
for why it's not going how you want
and keep our eyes fixed forward now that
my friends right there unfortunately the
message of self-discipline and personal
responsibility can leave you feeling
guilty and ashamed like you're not doing
good enough like you're not doing enough
like there's so much more that you could
be doing and so that's why on the flip
side again like I said
detaching from the outcome
being okay with
how things are accepting yourself just
as you are in this moment in time
with a Relentless pursuit to keep going
forward
and congratulating yourself
every single day even when you fall
short
even when you fail even when you mess up
when you can do both of those you have
the self-discipline you take personal
responsibility and yet you still
congratulate yourself for the little
things man
that's a recipe
to make you a millionaire
and so I hope this has encouraged you I
hope this helped you listen if you know
somebody that needs to hear this message
please share it with them
because
I know that this is going to change some
lives just hearing this right here
if you apply it so
that's what this podcast is for that's
why I do this
and so I'd encourage you since this is
free
you don't have to pay for this type of
information a lot of people charge for
this type of information I give it away
freely because I know that if you start
doing this it's going to affect
everything else and then you'll make
enough money to start hiring me to work
as a coach to hold you accountable to
support you we support people
better than any other organization or
business out there that does that does
this type of coaching for coaches and
course creators we're there to support
you to help you with your copywriting
with your ad writing with your campaigns
with your funnels to guide you to walk
you through each step and in our
coaching programs that's what we do we
hold your hand through the whole thing
that's what I'd love for you to do as
well that's what I'd love to help you
with as well so consider get on the
waiting list for one of our programs hop
into one of our free events that we're
doing
you won't regret it grow your life
everybody and we'll talk soon